A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Liaison Office, 2003-2010 (bulk 2006-2009).
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Virginia Liaison Office,
2003-2010 (bulk 2006-2009).
The Library of Virginia
44693
Virginia Liaison Office.
11.9 cu. ft. (34 boxes)
Biographical/Historical Information
The Virginia Liaison Office (VLO) represents the Governor before both Congress and the federal administration, advocating for the Commonwealth's interests in Washington, and monitoring federal developments that affect the state. The Office is responsible for monitoring and tracking federal legislation that is of interest to the Commonwealth and keeping the Governor's Office and state agencies up to date on the status of federal legislation and regulations. The Office is also tasked with influencing the development of federal legislation and regulations by keeping the Virginia Congressional Delegation informed about the Governor's priorities and maintaining contact with Congressinal staffs, key federal agency officials and public interest groups. Other duties include alerting state agencies and local government to federal grant opportunites and monitoring the progress of any grant applications, writing or advising on testimony to be presented by the Governor or state agency heads before Congressional committees, resolving administrative issues between state and federal agencies and maintaining liaison with other states and interstate groups. The VLO is also required to report twice a year to the Senate Finance Committee, the House Appropriations Committee and to the Governor's Office on all federal mandates and regulations which may have an affect on the Commonwealth. In addition to this, the VLO also works with interstate and regional organizations in which the Governor participates, such as the National Governor's Association, Southern Governor's Association, Appalachian Regional Commission, Southern States Energy Board, Southern Regional Education Board and the National Capital Region.
During the administration of Governor Timothy Kaine, Alfonso Lopez served as the Director of the Virginia Liaison Office (2006-2010) and Bennett Blodgett served as Deputy Director (2006-2009). Major issues during this administration included: American Recovery and Reinstatement Act (ARRA) and transit projects, Military Construction and Base Realignment and Closure (BRAC), Chesapeake Bay Revitalization, Climate Change, Dulles Corridor Metro Rail Project, Farm bill, Federal Unemployment Tax (FUTA), Foster Care, Health Insurance, Homeland Security, Housing, REAL ID, State Children's Health Insurance Program (SCHIP) reauthorization, Veterans Services, Wallops Research Park, and the Workforce Investment Act (WIA) and Workforce Development.
Scope and Content
The Virginia Liaison Office records, 2003-2010 (bulk 2006-2009), are housed in 34 boxes. The collection includes series for Director's correspondence and subject files, Policy Analyst correspondence and subject files, National Governors Association, and Southern Governors Association.
Issues of concern to the Virginia Liaison Office during the Kaine Administration include: BRAC, Byrne-Justice Assistance Grant (JAG) Program, Chesapeake Bay Revitalization, Child Care funding, Community Development Block Grant funding, Dulles Metro Rail Project, Eastern Shore Broadband, Federal Unemployment Tax Act (FUTA), Fort Monroe, Foster Care, Homeland Security, Land Conservation, Medicare and Medicaid, No Child Left Behince Act Reauthorization, REAL ID, State Children's Health Insurance Program (SCHIP), Virginia Wounded Warrior Program, and Wallops Island.
Alphabetical.
Related Material
OFFICE OF THE GOVERNOR-TIM KAINE
A Guide to the Governor Timothy M. Kaine Administration Electronic Files, Email, 2002-2010 (bulk 2006-2009). The Virginia Liaison Office Electronic Files series documents the electronic communication of the office during the Kaine administration. This series contains 20063 emails in ten (10) subseries. Subseries have been designated for: A. Alfonso Lopez Email, B. Bennett Blodgett Email, C. Eileen Filler-Corn Email, D. Dominic Gabello Email, E. Melinda Glazer Email, F. Aaron Turner Email, G. Kwame Boadi Email, H. Jessica Vasconcellos Email, I. Michele Alexander Email, and J. Mary Kuehler Email. There are no email files for Shaylah Nunn, Federal Policy Analyst. There are 14 protected and confidential emails that are restricted from public access per Code of Virginia, 42-1-78. Types of restricted information may include, but are not limited to: attorney-client communications and personnel information. The Library of Virginia Email Project - Governor Tim Kaine Portal provides access to the Kaine email collection and includes guides to other Kaine administration records.
The Governor Tim Kaine Administration Web Archive Collection, 2006-2010 contains archived versions of websites for the Governor's Office, his initiative sites, and the sites of his cabinet secretaries. Also included are the related sites for the First Lady (Anne Holton), as well as the Lt. Governor (Bill Bolling), and Attorney General (Bob McDonnell and William C. Mims), two statewide officials elected in the same cycle as Governor Kaine.
The Timothy M. Kaine Administration (2006-2010) Cabinet Weekly Reports Digital Collection contains the weekly reports submitted to the Governor and Chief of Staff by the Governor's Cabinet, including the Secretaries of Administration (Viola Baskerville), Agriculture and Forestry (Robert S. Bloxom), Commerce and Trade (Patrick O. Gottschalk), Commonwealth (Daniel C. LeBlanc, Jan-Mar. 2006 and Katherine K. Hanley (Mar. 2006-2010), Education (Dr. Thomas R. Morris), Finance (Jody Wagner, 2006-2008 and Richard D. Brown, 2008-2010), Health and Human Resources (Marilyn Tavenner), Natural Resources (Preston Bryant), Public Safety (John W. Marshall), Technology (Aneesh Chopra, 2006-2009 and Leonard M. Pomata, 2009-2010), and Transportation (Pierce Homer). Also included are reports by the Assistant to the Governor for Commonwealth Preparedness (Robert Crouch), Office of Constituent Services (Marc Cheatham, 2006-2007 and Amber Amato, 2007-2010), Press Office, Policy Office and Virginia Liaison Office. Reports were submitted each Thursday and placed in a binder for the Governor that he took with him at the end of the day on Friday. A second copy of the report was made for the Chief of Staff. The level of detail varied for each cabinet officer and items of importance were highlighted by staff for the Governor. Each report contains information on legislation, Governor's initiatives/special projects, agency matters/operations, events/agency visits, audits/investigations/compliance, stakeholder issues and pending decisions. Governor Kaine wrote handwritten notes and/or marked-up some reports with post-it notes and requested follow up information from the person submitting the report. Those questions and answers are included in this series. This series provides a weekly account of the issues and policy decisions of the Kaine Administration.
A Guide to the Governor Timothy M. Kaine, Executive Office-Governor, Records, 2005-2009. The Governor Timothy M. Kaine, Executive Office-Governor, Records are housed in 45 boxes. The collection is arranged into three (3) series. Series have been designated for: I. Weekly Status Reports; II. State Budget Files; and III. Briefing Binders and Reports. These records include agreements, briefing books, reports, correspondence, memorandums, budget documents, agendas, handouts, invitations, talking points, and speeches. This collection contains the weekly reports, briefing books and budgetary records of Governor Kaine (2006-2010).
A Guide to the Governor Timothy M. Kaine, Policy Office, Records, 2002-2010 (bulk 2006-2009). The Policy Office Records of Governor Timothy M. Kaine are housed in 174 boxes. The collection is arranged into five (5) series. Series have been designated for: I. Decision Briefs; II. Regulations; III. Legislative Files; IV. Executive Orders and Directives; and V. Policy Analyst Files. These records include agendas, decision briefs, correspondence, memorandums, legislative files, briefing books, meeting notes, subject files, reports, talking points and regulations. These records document the legislative and policy priorities of the Kaine administration (2006-2010). This collection also includes records from Governor Mark Warner's administration (2002-2006).
CABINET OFFICES
A Guide to the Records of the Office of Commonwealth Preparedness, 1989-2009 (bulk 2006-2009). The Office of Commonwealth Preparedness records consist of 37 archival boxes and are divided into eight series. Series have been designated for Cabinet Meeting Files, Commonwealth Interoperability Coordinator's Office Initiatives Files, Commonwealth Interoperability Coordinator's Office Subject files, Constituent Correspondence, Correspondence and Supporting Documentation, Homeland Security Files Grant, Meeting Files Preparedness Committees, and Robert P. Crouch Jr. Attorney Files. These records document the work of the Office of Commonwealth Preparedness. The bulk of the records can be found in the Correspondence and Supporting Documentation series related to base closings, campus security, hurricane preparedness, interoperability, the National Capital Region, and various office projects. Included are agendas, correspondence, minutes, newsletters, programs, reports, and surveys. Of note are the Constituent Correspondence and Correspondence and Supporting Documentation series which are invaluable in showing the concerns and interests of citizens, government officials, and other individuals regarding security, terrorism, and various other subjects.
A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 2005-2010. Contains records created and maintained by Secretary of Health and Human Resources, Marilyn B. Tavenner, during the administration of Governor Timothy M. Kaine. The records include incoming and outgoing correspondence with assigned agencies and constituents, subject files, decision memoranda, legislative files, budget material, and records related to activities and special projects.
A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Natural Resources, 1999-2010 (bulk 2006-2009). This collection contains the records, 1999-2010 (bulk 2006-2009), of the Office of Secretary of Natural Resources L. Preston Bryant, Jr., during the administration of Governor Tim Kaine. There is correspondence and subject files that relate to Secretary Bryant, the state agencies that he oversees, environmental organizations that operate in Virginia, and projects initiated by Governor Kaine. Legislative files contain material related to bills that were either under the purview of the Secretary of Natural Resources or upon which the Secretary wished to comment. Special programs include correspondence and subject files primarily created by Assistant Secretary of Natural Resources Missy Neff and Deputy Secretary of Natural Resources Nikki Rovner. Finally, there are speeches given by L. Preston Bryant, Jr., at public and private events.
A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Public Safety, 1990, 1992, 1996, 1998-2010 (bulk 2002-2009). The Secretary of Public Safety records consists of thirty-eight archival boxes and are divided into six series. Series have been designated for Correspondence-Assigned State Agencies, Correspondence and Supporting Documentation-Office of the Secretary, Decision Memoranda and Briefs, Federal Grant Funding, Legislative Files, and Special Projects and Studies. These records document the activities of the Office of the Secretary of Public Safety, as well as the agencies and boards which fall under its heading, during the gubernatorial terms of Governor Mark R. Warner (2002-2006) and Governor Timothy M. Kaine (2006-2010).
A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Transportation, 2006-2010. The Secretary of Transportation records consist of 52 archival boxes and are divided into 4 series. Series have been designated for Appointment Calendars (I), Constituent Correspondence (II), Legislative Files (III) and Special Projects and Studies (IV). These records document the work of the Secretary of Transportation Pierce Homer during the Kaine administration and were created or collected, 2006-2009, though some documents in this collection pre-date this time period.
Acquisition Information
Accession 44693 was transferred by the Office of the Governor, January 14, 2010.
Contents List
- Director's correspondence and subject files, 2003-2010., Extent: 3.85 cubic feet (11 boxes)
  This series includes the correspondence and subject files of Alfonso Lopez, Director of the Virginia Liaison Office, 2006-2010, and also includes some holdover files from the the previous Director, Jan Faircloth, 2002-2005. These files are arranged alphabetically by topic and include correspondence, the majority with congressmen, and federal and state officials, as well as event briefing materials, grants, legislation, meeting materials (agendas, briefs, notes, minutes, supporting documents), policies, presentations, promotional materials, proposals, publications, reference materials, reports, statistical summaries, and transcripts.
  - Director Alphonso Lopez, 2006-2010
    - American Recovery and Reinstatement Act, 2009. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Appalachian Regional Commission, 2006. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Appropriations FY2009, 2008. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Appropriations FY2010, 2008-2009. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Areva Enrichment Facility Project, 2007-2009. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Army Corps of Engineers projects (FY2009), 2006-2009. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Base Realignment and Closure (BRAC), 2006-2007. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Birthplace of Country Music Cultural Heritage Center, 2005-2007. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Black Bear Solid Waste Facility, 2006. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Boucher, Repr., meeting - Daniel Boone Interpretive and Vistors' Center, 2009. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission - Recommendations, 2006-2007. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Chesapeake Crescent, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Climate, 2008-2009. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Climate Change, 2007-2009. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Climate Change, 2009. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Climate Change - Global, 2007. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Climate Change - State Climatologist, 2006. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Coal and Mining, 2006-2007. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Commercial Fish and Shellfish Technologies (CFAST), 2007-2008. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Commonwealth Preparedness, 2005-2007. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Council on Virginia's Future, 2006. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Covanta Energy, 2007. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Disaster Mitigation, 2008. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Dam Rehabilitation and Repair Act, 2008. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Dominion Power Lines, 2006. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Ducks Unlimited - Chesapeake Bay, 2006. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Dulles Corridor Metro Rail Project (#1), 2006-2008. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Dulles Corridor Metro Rail Project (#2), 2006-2009. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Dulles Corridor Metro Rail Project (#3), 2007-2008. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Dulles Corridor Metro Rail Project - Extension to Whiele Avenue, 2007. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Dulles Greenway, 2007-2008. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Eastern Shore Broadband, 2007. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Economic Stimulus Package, 2008-2009. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Education, 2006-2007. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Energy Future, America's, undated. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Executive Leadership Retreat of Governor Timothy M. Kaine - Briefing binder, 2006 Jan 6. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - FAA Reauthorization - Reagan National Airport, undated. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Farm Bill, 2006-2007. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Farm Bill, 2008. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Farm Bill - Congressional Research Service (CRS) Reports, 2005-2006. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Farm Bill - Federal Farm Policy, 2006. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Farm Bill - Renewable Energy, 2001-2007. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Farm Bill - USDA Hearing, 2005. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Farm Bill - Virginia Workgroup, 2007. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Federal Disaster Relief, 2006. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Federal Issue Primer, 2009. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Federal Mandate Reports, 2006-2009. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Federal Unemployment Tax (FUTA) - Virginia Employment Commission (VEC), 2005-2007. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - FEMA and disasters, 2006. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Financial Regulatory Reform, 2009. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Ford Plant, 2006. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Fort Belvoir, 2006-2007. (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Fort Monroe, 2008. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Foster Care, 2007-2008. (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Franklin City - Flooding, 2006. (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - General Motors - Rolls Royce, 2009. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Great Dismal Swamp, 2007. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - H1N1 Flu, 2009. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - H-2B Guest Worker Program, 2008-2009. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Hanover County - I95 / Lewistown Interchange, 2007. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Hatcheries - Wytheville and Paint Bank, 2006. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Health Care Reform, 2009. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Health IT Council, 2008. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Health Policy Issues, 2006-2009. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - High Speed Rail, 2006-2009. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Homeland Security, 2007. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Homeland Security - Governor's meeting with U.S. Secretary of Homeland Security Michael Chertoff - Briefing binder, 2007 Mar 27. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Hot Lanes - I95/395/495, 2007-2009. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Housing, 2007-2008. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Housing - Governor's Housing Forum, 2009. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Housing - Governor's Housing Forum - Briefing binder, 2009 June 8. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - HUBZones, 2006-2007. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Immigration, 2006-2007. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Jefferson Labs, undated. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Journey Through Hallowed Ground National Heritage Act, 2005-2007. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Journey Through Hallowed Ground Partnership - Briefing for Gov. Kaine, Gov. Ehrlich and Mayor Williams, 2006 July 14. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Limited English Proficiency (No Child Left Behind), 2007. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Line Item Veto Legislation in the 109th Congress, 2006. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Local Public Assistance Cost Allocation Plans (LPACAP), 20. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Low-Income Home Energy Assistance Program (LIHEAP), 2005-2007. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Mayport, 2006-2009. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Medicaid, 2005-2007. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Medicaid, 2007-2008. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - National Capital Region - Homeland Security Senior Policy Group, 2006. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - National Capital Region - Leader's Meeting - Briefing binder, 2006 July 14. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - National Capital Tranportation Amendments, 2005-2006. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - National Guard, 2008. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - National Interest Electric Transmission Corridor (NIETC), 2007. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Natural Resources, 2006-2007. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Northern Virginia Transportation Commission, 2009. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Oceana, 2006. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Out-of-State Waste, 2006. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Outer Continental Shelf Drilling, 2006-2007. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Outlying Landing Field (OLF), 2007-2008. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Port Authority, 2006. (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Port Facilities, 2006. (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Potomac Appalachian Transmission Highline (PATH), 2009. (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Presidential Inauguration, 2009. (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Property Insurance, 2007. (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Public Private Partnerships, 2006-2008. (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Public Safety, 2006. (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Race to the Top (Education), 2009. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - REAL ID, 2006-2008. (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Recovery Act, 2009. (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Reformulated Gasoline (RFG), 2006. (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Renewable Fuel Standard, 2008. (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Rolls Royce, 2007. (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Southwest Virginia Power Station, 2006-2007. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Southwest Virginia Veterans Cemetery, 2007. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - State Children's Health Insurance Program (SCHIP), 2007. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS), 2007. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Task Force for the Prevention of Gangs, Mayor's (Chesapeake), 2007. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Telecommunication Bill, 2006. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Temporary Bridge - Advance Mills, Albemarle County, 2008. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Tourism - Capt. John Smith Trail, 2006. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Tourism - Virginia Coal Heritage Trail, undated. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Trade Adjustment Assistance (TAA), 2007. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Transportation, 2006-2009. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Transportation, Housing and Urban Development (THUD), 2009. (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Tribal Recognition, 2006-2008. (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Tribal Recognition, 2006-2009. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Tropical Storm Ernesto, 2006. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - USDA - Farm Service Agency closings, 2006. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Urban Area Security Initiative, 2006-2007. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Veterans Affairs, 20. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Information Technologies Agency (VITA), 2006. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Virginia-Israel Cooperation Agreement, 2008. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Tech, 2007. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Tech - Energy Efficiency, 2007-2008. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Voting Rights Act (VRA), 2006. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Wallops Island, 2006-2009. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Warner, Mark, 2008. (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (WMATA), 2008. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Wittman, Robert J., 2008. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Wolf, Frank R., 2006-2008. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Workforce Investment Act (WIA), 2006-2007. (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Yong Shu Li, 2007. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Director Jan Faircloth, 2002-2005
    - Amtrak, 2002-2003. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Atlantic Intercoastal Waterway (AIWW), 2004. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Biotechnology Partnership, 2003. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Birthplace of Country Music Museum, 2004-2005. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Chesapeake Bay, 2005. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission - Advisory Committee, 2005. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Chesapeake Bay Hill visits, 2005. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Children's Hospice International, 2005. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Clean Drinking Water Systems, 2002-2003. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Clean Water State Revolving Fund, 2004. (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Combs, C. Donald - Eastern Virginia Medical School, 2002. (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Community College System, 2002-2003. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Council of State Community Development Agencies (COSCDA), 2005. (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Disaster Declaration - Letter to President Bush, 2004. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Education Data Partnership, 2005. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Elizabeth River Project, 2003-2005. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Federal Mandate Reports, 2004-2006. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Fisheries Conservation, Wildlife and Oceans Subcommittee - Oversight Hearing on Chesapeake Bay in Your Community: A Restoration Plan, 2004. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Gang Growth in Virginia (Bob Crouch), 2004. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Gang of Five and Congressional Advisory Council meeting (Chesapeake Bay Foundation), 2004 Mar. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - GMMB - Maternal and Child Health Programs, 2005. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Health Care Reform, 2003-2005. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Health Coverage Tax Credits, 2004. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Homeland Security, 2005. (Box 10, Folder 6)